[{
    "id": 1,
    "question": "______ is crucial for enhancing productivity in todayâ€™s fast-paced world.",
    "answer": "Time management"
  },
  {
    "id": 2,
    "question": "The 80/20 Rule, also known as the ________, states that 80% of results come from 20% of efforts.",
    "answer": "Pareto Principle"
  },
  {
    "id": 3,
    "question": "The primary objective of time management is to increase _______.",
    "answer": "productivity"
  },
  {
    "id": 4,
    "question": "One common time management mistake is failing to keep a _________.",
    "answer": "To-Do List"
  },
  {
    "id": 5,
    "question": "Time management can help reduce _______ levels by organizing tasks and setting deadlines.",
    "answer": "stress"
  },
  {
    "id": 6,
    "question": "The principle that suggests that 20% of your tasks will often yield 80% of the results is referred to as the _______.",
    "answer": "80/20 Rule"
  },
  {
    "id": 7,
    "question": "One strategy to manage distractions is to turn off ________ or use tools that minimize interruptions.",
    "answer": "notifications"
  },
  {
    "id": 8,
    "question": "Effective time management is about focusing on tasks that truly contribute to your personal and professional _______.",
    "answer": "goals"
  },
  {
    "id": 9,
    "question": "The first step in effective time management is setting clear _______.",
    "answer": "goals"
  },
  {
    "id": 10,
    "question": "A major time-wasting habit that can lead to anxiety and missed deadlines is _______.",
    "answer": "procrastination"
  }
]
